# Jamie Joseph Heiney

# Controller for Construction Company

### **About Me**

Experienced accountant with a passion for simplifying complex topics. Skilled in bank & credit card reconciliation, QuickBooks (Enterprise and Online), Google Sheets, Excel cash flow management, budgeting and financial planning. Strong communication skills and experience in managing accounts payable and creating financial reports for multiple companies. Also experienced in creating interactive group games for elderly care facilities.

#### Skills

- Bank & Credit Card Reconciliation
- Excel Cash Flow Management
- · Simplification of complex topics
- QuickBooks (Enterprise and Online)
- Budgeting and Financial Planning
- · Google Sheets
- Excellent communication

#### Experience

# Accountant at Alpha Capital LLC

Dec 2019 - May 2022

- Served as an accountant for several capital funding companies, managing all their bookkeeping needs. Including creating chart of
  accounts, bank reconciliation. Organized, formatted, and imported large amounts of data from CRMS, other software and google
  sheets.
- Designed and implemented a comprehensive loan tracking system using multiple interlinked Google Sheets and Google App Scripts. The system allowed owners, salespeople, and outside investors to view and update vital information about current and former deals, with multiple permission levels and an intuitive UI.
- Utilized the accounting system for multiple companies owned by Alpha Capital and provided consulting services to other companies.

#### Nursing Home Game Creator at Games 4 Life

Feb 2017 - Feb 2019

- Developed interactive group games for elderly care facilities to address the lack of stimulating and engaging content for elders.
- Grew client base to over 30 nursing homes and hundreds of happy users.
- Managed accounts receivable and gained a broad understanding of business and management.

#### AP Regional Manager at Beyond Healthcare LLC

Jan 2015 - Mar 2017

- Oversaw AP transactions and personnel for four nursing homes.
- Negotiated with vendors for more favorable contracts.
- Maintained all accounts payable reports, spreadsheets, and files.
- Acted as a liaison between corporate and nursing home accounts payable departments.
- Managed emails and website domains for the corporate staff.

#### Education

# Certificate - Accounting Foundations: Bookkeeping QuickBooks Online Essential Training

Yeshiva Toras Chaim High School

Certificate course completed in Accounting Foundations: Bookkeeping QuickBooks Online Essential Training

# Diploma

May 2008

Dual Enrollment Florida International University Accounting Course: Accounting Coach course by Harold Averkamp Tested and received

Contact: 305-801-7497